linkconnector.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy | LinkConnector

## A. About Us

The LinkConnector (LC) Website is an online marketing platform providing services (the “ **Services** “) to Affiliates and Merchants operated by LinkConnector Corporation, a company headquartered in the State of North Carolina in the United States (“ **we** ,” “ **us** ,” “ **our** ,” and “ **LinkConnector** “).

The Services enable our Customers to, among other things, create and manage online campaigns, interact with other Customers, and place advertisements on various sites around the web. Find out more about our Services here.

## B. Key Terms

In this privacy policy, these terms have the following meanings:

“ **Affiliate** ” means a person or company that agrees to promote Services in exchange for a payment.

“ **Customer** ” means any person or entity that is registered with us to use the Services.  Customers are further delineated as Affiliates and Merchants.

“ **Merchant** ” means a person or company that create an offer or campaign through LinkConnector and agrees to pay Affiliates for promoting Services.

“ **Personal Information** ” means any information that identifies or can be used to identify a Customer, a User, or a Visitor, directly or indirectly. Examples of Personal Information include, but are not limited to, first and last name, email address, occupation, or other demographic information.

“ **Relationship** ” means an agreement between an Affiliate and Merchant to promote Services in exchange for a commission.

“ **Services** ” means the product(s) or service(s) offered by the Merchant and promoted by the Affiliate.

“ **Website(s)** ” means any website(s) we own and operate (such as www.LinkConnector.com) or any web pages, interactive features, applications, widgets, blogs, social networks, social network “tabs,” or other online, mobile, or wireless offerings that post a link to this privacy policy.

“ **User** ” is any person who engages with our tracking or Websites.

“ **Visitor** ” means any person who visits any of our Websites.

“ **you** ” and “ **your** ” means, depending on the context, either a Customer, a User, or a Visitor.

This section applies to the Personal Information we collect and process from a Customer or potential Customer through the provision of the Services. If you are not a Customer, the Users or Visitors section of this policy may be more applicable to you and your data.  **In this section, “you” and “your” refer to Customers and potential Customers.**

## A. Information We Collect

The Personal Information that we may collect broadly falls into the following categories:

### i. Information you provide to us

While engaging with our Services, you may provide Personal Information about you and team members. Personal Information is often, but not exclusively, provided to us when you sign up for and use the Services, consult with our customer service team, send us an email, integrate the Services with another website or service (for example, when you choose to connect your e-commerce shopping cart with LinkConnector), or communicate with us in any other way.

By giving us this information, you agree to this information being collected, used, and disclosed as described in our Terms and Conditions and in this privacy policy.  
This information may include:

  * **Registration information** : You need a LinkConnector account to use the Services as a Customer. When you register for an account, you will be asked to provide certain basic information, such as your name, email address, username, password, company name, occupation, location, and phone number.
  * **Billing and communications information** : If you purchase our Services, you may also need to provide us with payment and billing information, such as your credit card details and billing address. LinkConnector will also maintain a record of your billing transactions and purchases, and any communications and responses.

### ii. Information we collect automatically

When you use the Services, we may automatically collect certain information about your device and usage of the Services. We use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect some of this information. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies is discussed more below in Cookies and Tracking Technologies.  
This information may include:

  * **Device information** : We collect information about the device and applications you use to access the Services, such as your IP address, your operating system, your browser ID, and other information about your system and connection.
  * **Log data** : Our web servers keep log files that record data each time a device accesses those servers and those log files contain data about the nature of each access, including originating IP addresses. We may also access metadata and other information associated with files that you upload into our Services.
  * **Product usage data** : We collect usage data about you whenever you interact with our Services, which may include the dates and times you access the Services and your browsing activities (such as what portions of the Services are used). We also collect information regarding the performance of the Services, including metrics related to the deliverability of emails and other communications you send through the Services. This information allows us to improve the content and operation of the Services and facilitate research and analysis of the Services.

### iii. Information we collect from other sources

From time to time, we may obtain information about you from third-party sources, such as public databases, social media platforms, third-party data providers and our joint marketing partners. We take steps to ensure that such third parties are legally or contractually permitted to disclose such information to us.

Examples of the information we receive from other sources include device information (such as IP addresses), location (such as city and state), and online behavioral data (such as information about use of social media websites, page view information and search results and links). We use this information, alone or in combination with other information (including Personal Information) we collect, to enhance our ability to provide relevant marketing and content to you and to develop and provide you with more relevant products, features, and services.

## B. Use of Personal Information

We may use the Personal Information we collect through the Services or other sources for a range of reasons, including:

  * **To bill and collect money owed to us by you.**   This includes sending you emails, invoices, receipts, notices of delinquency, and alerting you if we need a different credit card number. We use third parties for secure credit card transaction processing, and those third parties collect billing information to process your orders and credit card payments. To learn more about the steps we take to safeguard that data, see the Our Security section of this privacy policy.
  * **To send you system alert messages.**   For example, we may inform you about temporary or permanent changes to our Services, such as planned outages, or send you account, security or compliance notifications, such as new features, version updates, releases, abuse warnings, and changes to this privacy policy.
  * **To communicate with you about your account and provide customer support.**
  * **To enforce compliance with our Terms and Conditions and applicable law** , and to protect the rights and safety of our Customers and third parties, as well as our own. This may include developing tools and algorithms that help us prevent violations.
  * **To meet legal requirements** , including complying with court orders, valid discovery requests, valid subpoenas, and other appropriate legal mechanisms.
  * **To provide information to representatives and advisors** , including attorneys and accountants, to help us comply with legal, accounting, or security requirements.
  * **To prosecute and defend a court, arbitration, or similar legal proceeding.**
  * **To respond to lawful requests by public authorities** , including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
  * **To provide, support and improve the Services.**  For example, this may include sharing your information with third parties to provide and support our Services or to make certain features of the Services available to you.
  * **To provide suggestions to you.**   This includes using data to suggest using data to suggest products or services that you may be interested in or that may be relevant to you or your Relationships.
  * **Other purposes.**  To carry out other legitimate business purposes, as well as other lawful purposes about which we will notify you.

## C. Other Data Protection Rights

You have the following data protection rights:

  * To **access, correct, update or request deletion**  of Personal Information. LinkConnector takes reasonable steps to ensure that the data we collect is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete and up to date. As a Customer, you can manage many of your individual account and profile settings within the dashboard provided through the LinkConnector platform, or you may contact us using the contact details provided in Questions & Concerns. You can also manage information about your Relationships within the dashboard provided through the LinkConnector platform to assist you with responding to requests to access, correct, update or delete information that you receive.
  * Similarly, if Personal Information is collected or processed based on consent, the data subject can withdraw their consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your Personal Information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
  * In addition, individuals who are residents of the European Economic Area (EEA) can object to processing of their Personal Information, ask to restrict processing of their Personal Information or request portability of their Personal Information. You can exercise these rights by contacting us using the contact details provided in the Questions & Concerns section below.

We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection law. We may ask you to verify your identity to help us respond efficiently to your request.

This section applies to the information we process about our Users as a data controller pursuant to our legitimate business interests, as explained in the Legal Basis for Processing section below. Our Services are intended for use by our Customers. As a result, for much of the Personal Information we collect and process about Users through the Services, we act as a processor on behalf of our Customers. LinkConnector is not responsible for the privacy or security practices of our Customers, which may differ from those set forth in this privacy policy. Please check with individual Customers about the policies they have in place.  **For purposes of this section, “you” and “your” refer to Users.**

## A. Information We Collect

The Personal Information that we may collect or receive about you broadly falls into the following categories:

### i. Information we collect automatically

When you engage with the Services, we may automatically collect certain information about your device and usage of the Services. We use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect some of this information. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies is discussed more below in Cookies and Tracking Technologies.  
This information may include:

  * **Device information** : We collect information about the device and applications you use to access the Services, such as your IP address, your operating system, your browser ID, and other information about your system and connection.
  * **Product usage data** : We collect usage data about you whenever you interact with our Services, which may include the dates and times you access the Services and your browsing activities (such as what portions of the Services are used). We also collect information regarding the performance of the Services, including metrics related to the deliverability of emails and other communications you send through the Services. This information allows us to improve the content and operation of the Services and facilitate research and analysis of the Services.

## B. Use of Personal Information

We may use the Personal Information we collect or receive about you for our legitimate business interests, including:

  * **To enforce compliance with our Terms and Conditions and applicable law.** This may include developing tools and algorithms that help us prevent violations.
  * **To protect the rights and safety of our Customers and third parties** , as well as our own. For example, sometimes we review the content of our Customers’ campaigns to make sure they comply with our Terms and Conditions. To improve that process, we have software that helps us find promotions or campaigns that may violate our Terms and Conditions.
  * **To meet legal requirements** , including complying with court orders, valid discovery requests, valid subpoenas, and other appropriate legal mechanisms.
  * **To provide information to representatives and advisors** , including attorneys and accountants, to help us comply with legal, accounting, or security requirements.
  * **To prosecute and defend a court, arbitration** , or similar legal proceeding.
  * **To respond to lawful requests by public authorities** , including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
  * **To provide, support and improve the Services.**  For example, this may include sharing your information with third parties to provide and support our Services or to make certain features of the Services available to you.
  * **Other purposes.**  To carry out other legitimate business purposes, as well as other lawful purposes about which we will notify you.

## C. Other Data Protection Rights

You have the following data protection rights:

  * To  **access, correct, update or request deletion**  of your Personal Information. LinkConnector takes reasonable steps to ensure that the data we collect is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete, and up to date. You may contact us directly at any time about accessing, correcting, updating or deleting your Personal Information, or altering your data, by contacting us using the contact details provided in Questions & Concerns. We will consider your request in accordance with applicable laws.
  * In addition, if you are a resident of the EEA, LinkConnector has decided to  **restrict storing**  of your Personal Information and will anonymize any Personal Information we collect from you.
  * As described above, for much of the Personal Information we collect and process about Users through the Services, we act as a processor on behalf of our Customers. In such cases, if you are a User and want to exercise any data protection rights that may be available to you under applicable law or have questions or concerns about how your Personal Information is handled by LinkConnector as a processor on behalf of our individual Customers, you should contact the relevant Customer that is using the LinkConnector Services and refer to their separate privacy policies.

We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws. We may ask you to verify your identity to help us respond efficiently to your request.

This section applies to Personal Information that we collect and process through our Websites and in the usual course of our business, such as in connection with our recruitment, events, sales and marketing activities.  **In this section “you” and “your” refers to Visitors.**

## A. Information We Collect

### i. Information you provide to us on the Websites or otherwise

Certain parts of our Websites may ask you to provide Personal Information voluntarily. For example, we may ask you to provide certain Personal Information (such as your name, contact details, company name, profile information) to sign up for a free or paid LinkConnector account, apply for a role with LinkConnector, or otherwise submit inquiries to us. We may also collect Personal Information, such as your contact and job details and feedback, when you attend our events, take part in surveys, or through other business or marketing interactions we may have with you. You may choose to provide additional information when you communicate with us or otherwise interact with us, and we will keep copies of any such communications for our records.

The Personal Information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your Personal Information. We will also let you know prior to collection whether the provision of the Personal Information we are collecting is compulsory or may be provided on a voluntary basis and the consequences, if any, of not providing the information.

### ii. Information we collect automatically through the Websites

When you visit our Websites, we may also collect certain information automatically from your device. In some countries, including countries in the European Economic Area, this information may be considered Personal Information under applicable data protection laws.

Specifically, the information we collect automatically may include your IP address, your operating system, your browser ID, your browsing activity, and other information about your system and connection and how you interact with our Websites and other websites. We may collect this information as a part of log files as well as through the use of cookies or other tracking technologies. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies is discussed more below in Cookies and Tracking Technologies.

## B. Use of Personal Information

We may use the information we collect through our Websites for a range of reasons, including:

  * **To provide, operate, optimize, and maintain our Websites.**
  * **To send you information for marketing purposes** , in accordance with your marketing preferences.
  * **For recruitment purposes if you have applied for a role with LinkConnector.**
  * **To respond to your online inquiries and requests** , and to provide you with information and access to resources or services that you have requested from us.
  * **To manage our Websites and system administration and security.**
  * **To improve the navigation and content of our Websites.**
  * **To identify any server problems or other IT or network issues.**
  * **To process transactions and to set up online accounts.**
  * **To compile aggregated statistics about site usage and to better understand the preferences of our Visitors.**
  * **To carry out research and development to improve our products and services.**
  * **To customize content and layout of the Websites.**
  * **To carry out other legitimate business purposes** , as well as other lawful purposes.

In addition, we may combine Personal Information with other information we collect or obtain about you (such as information we source from our third-party partners) to serve you specifically, such as to deliver a product or service according to your preferences or restrictions, or for advertising or targeting purposes in accordance with this privacy policy. When we combine Personal Information with other information in this way, we treat it as, and apply all the safeguards in this privacy policy applicable to, Personal Information.

## C. Public Information and Third-Party Websites

  * **Blog.**  We have a public blog on our LinkConnector.com. Any information you include in a comment on our blog may be read, collected, and used by anyone. If your Personal Information appears on our blog and you want it removed, contact us using the contact details provided in Questions & Concerns. If we are unable to remove your information, we will tell you why.
  * **Social media platforms and widgets.**  Our Websites include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button. These features may collect information about your IP address and which page you are visiting on our Website, and they may set a cookie to make sure the feature functions properly.  Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Website. We also maintain presences on social media platforms, including Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn. Any information, communications, or materials you submit to us via a social media platform is done at your own risk without any expectation of privacy. We cannot control the actions of other users of these platforms or the actions of the platforms themselves. Your interactions with those features and platforms are governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide them.
  * **Links to third-party websites.**  Our Websites include links to other websites, whose privacy practices may be different from ours. If you submit Personal Information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.

## D. Other Data Protection Rights

You have the following data protection rights:

  * To  **access, correct, update, or request deletion**  of your Personal Information. LinkConnector takes reasonable steps to ensure that the data we collect is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete, and up to date. You may contact us directly at any time about accessing, correcting, updating, or deleting your Personal Information, or altering your data or marketing preferences by contacting us using the contact details provided in Questions & Concerns. We will consider your request in accordance with applicable laws.
  * In addition, if you are a resident of the EEA, LinkConnector has decided to  **restrict storing**  of your Personal Information and will anonymize any Personal Information we collect from you.
  * Similarly, if we have collected and processed your Personal Information with your consent, then you can  **withdraw your consent**  at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your Personal Information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws. We may ask you to verify your identity to help us respond efficiently to your request.

## A. How We Share Information

We may share and disclose your Personal Information to the following types of third parties for the purposes described in this privacy policy  **(for purposes of this section, “you” and “your” refer to Customers, Users, and Visitors unless otherwise indicated)** :

### i. Our service providers

Sometimes, we share your information with our third-party service providers, who help us provide and support our Services and other business-related functions.

### ii. Advertising partners

We may partner with third-party advertising networks and exchanges to display advertising on our Websites or to manage and serve our advertising on other sites and may share Personal Information with them for this purpose.

We and our third-party partners may use cookies and other tracking technologies, such as pixels and web beacons, to gather information about your activities on our Websites and other sites to provide you with targeted advertising based on your browsing activities and interests. For more information about cookies and other tracking technologies, please see Cookies and Tracking Technologies.

### iii. Any competent law enforcement body, regulatory body, government agency, court or other third party

Where we believe disclosure is necessary (a) as a matter of applicable law or regulation, (b) to exercise, establish, or defend our legal rights, or (c) to protect your vital interests or those of any other person.

### iv. A potential buyer (and its agents and advisors)

In the case of a sale, merger, consolidation, liquidation, reorganization, or acquisition.

In that event, any acquirer will be subject to our obligations under this privacy policy.

### v. Any other person with your consent.

## B. Cookies and Tracking Technologies

We and our partners may use various technologies to collect and store information when you use our Services, and this may include using cookies and similar tracking technologies, such as pixels and web beacons. For example, we use web beacons on Merchant confirmation pages which signal the completion of a transaction. These web beacons allow us to collect information such as the recipient’s IP address, browser, order information, and other similar details. We use this information to help us determine if a commissionable event has occurred. Reports are also available to Customers when we process this information, so we may collect and review that information.

Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies is discussed in more detail in our Cookie Policy and Tracking Technologies Guide.

## C. Legal Basis for Processing

We process Personal Information about you as a data controller as described in this section, where such processing is in our  **legitimate interests**  and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms. Our legitimate interests typically include: improving, maintaining, providing, and enhancing our technology, products and services; ensuring the security of the Services and our Website; and for our marketing activities.

We will normally collect and use Personal Information from you where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data-protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms.

Typically, our legitimate interests include improving, maintaining, providing, and enhancing our technology, products, and services; ensuring the security of the Services and our Websites; and for our marketing activities.

If you are a Customer, we may need Personal Information to  **perform in our relationship** with you. In some limited cases, we may also have a  **legal obligation**  to collect Personal Information from you.

If we ask you to provide Personal Information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contact with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your Personal Information is mandatory or not, as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your Personal Information.  
Where required by law, we will collect Personal Information only where we have your  **consent**  to do so.

If you have questions about or need further information concerning the legal basis on which we collect and use your Personal Information, please contact us using the contact details provided in Questions & Concerns section below.

### i. EEA Persons Only

For the purposes of applicable EU data protection law (including the General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (the “ **GDPR** “), we are a ‘data controller’ of your personal information.  
You have the  **right to complain to a data protection authority**  about our collection and use of your Personal Information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority. Contact details for data protection authorities in the EEA are available [here](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm).

## D. Your Choices and Opt-Outs

### i. Email

Customers and Visitors who receive our marketing emails can opt-out of receiving marketing emails from us at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of our marketing messages.

Also, all opt-out requests can be made by emailing us using the contact details provided in the Questions & Concerns section below. Please note that some communications (such as service messages, account notifications, billing information) are considered transactional and necessary for account management, and Customers cannot opt-out of these messages unless you cancel your LinkConnector account.

### ii. Data

Users and Visitors may opt-out of data storage, but Customers cannot.  Given the nature of the Customer relationship, the data we store is vital to that relationship.

If you are a resident of the EEA, LinkConnector has decided to  **restrict** **storing**  of your Personal Information and will anonymize any Personal Information we collect from you.

If you are not in the EEA, you can opt-out of data storage by clicking here.

### iii. Tracking

You may opt-out of tracking.  To understand more about our tracking and your ability to opt-out you should review our Tracking Technologies Guide.

## E. Our Security

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect personal information relating to you, we cannot guarantee the security of such data transmitted to the Website; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received personal information relating to you, we use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access.

All information you provide to LinkConnector is stored on secure servers. Any payment transactions carried out by us or our chosen third-party provider of payment processing services will be encrypted industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring or receiving personal information, such as SSL technology. The safety and security of your information and any personal information relating to you also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password that enables you to access certain parts of the Website and/or the Services, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

We take appropriate and reasonable technical and organizational measures to protect Personal Information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction, considering the risks involved in the processing and the nature of the Personal Information. If you have any questions about the security of your Personal Information, you may contact us using the contact details provided in Questions & Concerns.

LinkConnector accounts require a username and password to log in. Customers must keep their username and password secure, and never disclose it to a third party. Because the information in a Customer’s LinkConnector account is so sensitive, account passwords are hashed, which means we cannot see a Customer’s password. We cannot resend forgotten passwords either. We will only provide Customers with instructions on how to reset them.

We will safeguard, according to strict standards of security and confidentiality, any information our Customers and Visitors share with us.

Access to any of our data is via a Username and Password by Affiliates and Merchants, or by authorized LinkConnector employees, who are trained in the proper handling of customer information, to have access to that information. Employees who violate our Privacy Policy will be subject to our normal disciplinary process and subject to dismissal.

## F. International Transfers

### i. We operate in the United States

Our secure servers and offices are located in the United States, so your information may be transferred to, stored, or processed in the United States. While the data protection, privacy, and other laws of the United States might not be as comprehensive as those in your country, we take extraordinary steps to protect your privacy.

### ii. Customers, Users, and Visitors located outside the United States

If you are someone who lives outside the United States:

  * Where we say we assume an obligation about Personal Information, we are also requiring our subcontractors to undertake a similar obligation, where relevant.
  * We will not use or disclose Personal Information for the purpose of our direct marketing to you unless you have consented to receive direct marketing; you would reasonably expect us to use your personal details for the marketing; or we believe you may be interested in the material, but it is impractical for us to obtain your consent. You may opt out of any marketing materials we send to you through an unsubscribe mechanism or by contacting us directly. If you have requested not to receive further direct marketing messages, we may continue to provide you with messages that are not regarded as “direct marketing” including changes to our terms, system alerts, and other information related to your account.
  * Our secure servers are located in the United States. In addition, we or our subcontractors may use cloud technology to store or process Personal Information. It is not practicable for us to specify in advance which country will have jurisdiction over this type of activity.
  * If you think the information we hold about you is inaccurate, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant, or misleading, we will take reasonable steps to correct that information upon your request.

## G. Retention of Data

We retain Personal Information where we have an ongoing legitimate business or legal need to do so. Our retention periods will vary depending on the type of data involved, but, generally, we’ll refer to these criteria to determine retention period:

  * Whether we have a legal or contractual need to retain the data.
  * Whether the data is necessary to provide our Services.
  * Whether our Customers can access and delete the data within their LinkConnector accounts.
  * Whether our Customers would reasonably expect that we would retain the data until they remove it or until their LinkConnector accounts are closed or terminated.

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your Personal Information, we will either delete or anonymize it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your Personal Information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your Personal Information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

## H. California Privacy

Under California Law, California residents have the right to request in writing from businesses with whom they have an established business relationship, (a) a list of the categories of Personal Information, such as name, email, and mailing address, and the type of services provided to the customer that a business has disclosed to third parties (including affiliates that are separate legal entities) during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third-parties’ direct marketing purposes, and (b) the names and addresses of all such third parties. To request the above information, please contact us using the contact details provided in Questions & Concerns.

## I. Children and Our Services

Our services are not directed to children, and you may not use our services if you are under the age of 18. You must also be old enough to consent to the processing of your personal data in your country (in some countries we may allow your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf). You must be at least 18 years of age to become a LinkConnector Customer.

## J. Changes to this Policy

We may change this policy at any time and from time to time. The most recent version of the policy is reflected by the version date located at the top of this policy. All updates and amendments are effective immediately upon notice, which we may give by any means, including, but not limited to, by posting a revised version of this policy or other notice on the Websites. We encourage you to review this policy often to stay informed of changes that may affect you. Our electronically or otherwise properly stored copies of this policy are each deemed to be the true, complete, valid, authentic, and enforceable copy of the version of this policy that was in effect on each respective date you visited the Website.

## K. Questions & Concerns

If you have any questions or comments, or if you have a concern about the way in which we have handled any privacy matter, please send a message to . You may also contact us by postal mail at:

LinkConnector Corporation  
Attn. Privacy Officer  
8000 Weston Parkway  
Suite 340  
Cary, NC 27513  
**For EEA Residents:**  
For the purposes of EU data protection legislation, LinkConnector Corporation is the controller of your Personal Information. Our Data Protection Officer can be contacted at .
